This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>The Indian ExpressSports – The Indian Express</title>
<atom:link href="http://indianexpress.com/section/sports/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<link>http://indianexpress.com</link>
<description>
Latest News, Breaking News Live, Current Headlines, India News Online
</description>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 21:09:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<language>en</language>
<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
<generator>http://wordpress.com/</generator>
<cloud domain="indianexpress.com" port="80" path="/?rsscloud=notify" registerProcedure="" protocol="http-post"/>
<image>
<url>
http://0.gravatar.com/blavatar/efe0300e7f891c5c802ed340f6b20b67?s=96&d=http%3A%2F%2Fs2.wp.com%2Fi%2Fbuttonw-com.png
</url>
<title>Sports – The Indian Express</title>
<link>http://indianexpress.com</link>
</image>
<atom:link rel="search" type="application/opensearchdescription+xml" href="http://indianexpress.com/osd.xml" title="The Indian Express"/>
<atom:link rel="hub" href="http://indianexpress.com/?pushpress=hub"/>
<item>
<title>
Engine problems force Lewis Hamilton to back of China grid
</title>
<link>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/motor-sport/engine-problems-force-lewis-hamilton-to-back-of-china-grid-2756462/
</link>
<comments>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/motor-sport/engine-problems-force-lewis-hamilton-to-back-of-china-grid-2756462/#respond
</comments>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 17:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 17:49:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</dc:creator>
<category>
<![CDATA[ Motor Sport ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ Sports ]]>
</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
http://indianexpress.com/?post_type=article&p=2756462
</guid>
<description>
<![CDATA[
Lewis Hamilton will start Chinese Grand Prix from last place on the grid as his team-mate Nico Rosberg took pole.<img alt="" border="0" src="http://pixel.wp.com/b.gif?host=indianexpress.com&#038;blog=53855017&#038;post=2756462&#038;subd=indianexpressonline&#038;ref=&#038;feed=1" width="1" height="1" />
]]>
</description>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img class="wp-image-2756489 size-full" src="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/hamilton_ap-m.jpg" alt="Lewis Hamilton" /> Lewis Hamilton already carrying a five-place grid penalty for a change of gearbox. (Source: AP) <p>World champion Lewis Hamilton will start the Chinese Grand Prix from the back of the grid after failing to set a time in qualifying on Saturday due to engine problems with his Mercedes.</p> <p>Hamilton, already carrying a five-place grid penalty for a change of gearbox, complained about a lack of engine power during the opening 18-minute phase of qualifying.</p> <p>The Briton went out late in the session, which was interrupted by a 20-minute red flag stoppage following a crash for<br /> Manor rookie Pascal Wehrlein, but headed back into the pits again.</p> <p>&#8220;These things are sent to try us and I am sure we will learn from it. It is just about trying to figure out the issue and making sure it doesn&#8217;t happen again,&#8221; Hamilton told Britain&#8217;s SkySports.</p> <p>&#8220;The car is quick, hopefully they get the issue fixed and we can have a race tomorrow.&#8221;</p> <p>Hamilton hasn&#8217;t won a race since October&#8217;s U.S. Grand Prix and trails team mate Nico Rosberg, winner of the opening two races of the season, by 17 points in the standings.</p> <p>He arrived in China, where he has won a record won four races, hoping to turn the tide by racing to his third successive Shanghai win despite his gearbox penalty.</p><img alt="" border="0" src="http://pixel.wp.com/b.gif?host=indianexpress.com&#038;blog=53855017&#038;post=2756462&#038;subd=indianexpressonline&#038;ref=&#038;feed=1" width="1" height="1" />
]]>
</content:encoded>
<wfw:commentRss>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/motor-sport/engine-problems-force-lewis-hamilton-to-back-of-china-grid-2756462/feed/
</wfw:commentRss>
<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
<media:thumbnail url="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/hamilton_ap-f.jpg?w=450"/>
<media:content url="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/hamilton_ap-f.jpg?w=450" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">Lewis Hamilton</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://0.gravatar.com/avatar/0a187292f2964e780b199c455fa75653?s=96&d=identicon&r=G" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">somyakapoor</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="https://indianexpressonline.files.wordpress.com/2016/04/hamilton_ap-m.jpg" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">Lewis Hamilton</media:title>
</media:content>
</item>
<item>
<title>Positive start by Indian shooters in Rio World Cup</title>
<link>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/sport-others/positive-start-by-indian-shooters-in-rio-world-cup-2756433/
</link>
<comments>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/sport-others/positive-start-by-indian-shooters-in-rio-world-cup-2756433/#respond
</comments>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 17:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 17:32:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</dc:creator>
<category>
<![CDATA[ Sport Others ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ Sports ]]>
</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
http://indianexpress.com/?post_type=article&p=2756433
</guid>
<description>
<![CDATA[
In the first qualification round of the men's trap event, former world champion and world number one Manavjit missed two targets out of 50.<img alt="" border="0" src="http://pixel.wp.com/b.gif?host=indianexpress.com&#038;blog=53855017&#038;post=2756433&#038;subd=indianexpressonline&#038;ref=&#038;feed=1" width="1" height="1" />
]]>
</description>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img class="size-full wp-image-2756480" src="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/manavjit-singh-sandhu-m.jpg" alt="Manavjit Singh Sandhu, Kynan Chenai, ISSF tournament, ISSF tournament updates, ISSF tournament news, sports news, sports" /> Manavjit Singh Sandhu got off to positive starts on day one of competition at the International Shooting<br />Sport Federation World Cup. (Source: Express File) <p>Indian trap shooters Manavjit Singh Sandhu and Kynan Chenai got off to positive starts on day one of competition at the International Shooting Sport Federation World Cup in Rio de Janeiro.</p> <p>The ISSF tournament for rifle, pistol and shotgun assumes significance as it is considered a test event before the Rio Olympic Games in August.</p> <p>In the first qualification round of the men&#8217;s trap event, former world champion and world number one Manavjit missed two targets out of 50 to end the day at eighth position.</p> <p>Youngster Chenai, who will be going to his first Olympics, was a point below, shooting a score of 47 to lie in 14th position.</p> <p>There are 75 more targets to go before the top six make it to the final round, scheduled for Sunday.</p> <p>The two top trap shooters in the world, Alberto Fernandez (ranked number two) of Spain and Giovanni Cernogoraz (ranked number one) of Croatia shot scores of 50 and 49 respectively to end in first and third positions on the leaderboard.</p> <p>Jiri Liptak of the Czech Republic also shot a perfect 50 to share the lead with Alberto.</p> <p>The other Indian in the men&#8217;s trap, Zoravar Singh Sandhu was lying in 25th place after shooting a first day total of 46.</p> <p>Also, in the women&#8217;s trap event, India&#8217;s Seema Tomar shot a score of 41 to end the first day of qualification in 19th place.</p> <p>Finals of women&#8217;s trap scheduled later on Saturday local time.</p> <p>The Olympic Shooting Centre, located inside the Deodoro Park, one of three venue clusters for the Games, is hosting 15 finals with the men&#8217;s 10m air rifle kicking off the race for the medals.</p> <p>Each day have at least one final concluding with the men&#8217;s skeet on April 24.</p> <p>Around 650 shooters from 88 countries are participating in the tournament.</p><img alt="" border="0" src="http://pixel.wp.com/b.gif?host=indianexpress.com&#038;blog=53855017&#038;post=2756433&#038;subd=indianexpressonline&#038;ref=&#038;feed=1" width="1" height="1" />
]]>
</content:encoded>
<wfw:commentRss>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/sport-others/positive-start-by-indian-shooters-in-rio-world-cup-2756433/feed/
</wfw:commentRss>
<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
<media:thumbnail url="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/manavjit-singh-sandhu-f.jpg?w=450"/>
<media:content url="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/manavjit-singh-sandhu-f.jpg?w=450" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">Manavjit Singh Sandhu at shooting range in Mohali</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://0.gravatar.com/avatar/3bfbb228f2cd05d4c81e005d0a694622?s=96&d=identicon&r=G" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">tanujlakhina</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="https://indianexpressonline.files.wordpress.com/2016/04/manavjit-singh-sandhu-m.jpg" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">
Manavjit Singh Sandhu, Kynan Chenai, ISSF tournament, ISSF tournament updates, ISSF tournament news, sports news, sports
</media:title>
</media:content>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Harbhajan Singh can take his villa whenever he wants, says Amrapali CMD
</title>
<link>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/harbhajan-singh-can-take-his-villa-whenever-he-wants-says-amrapali-cmd-2756276/
</link>
<comments>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/harbhajan-singh-can-take-his-villa-whenever-he-wants-says-amrapali-cmd-2756276/#respond
</comments>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 15:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 15:41:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</dc:creator>
<category>
<![CDATA[ Cricket ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ Sports ]]>
</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
http://indianexpress.com/?post_type=article&p=2756276
</guid>
<description>
<![CDATA[
Harbhajan Singh's villa is allotted. He can take it whenever he wants.I stand by my gift, said Anil Sharma, Amarpali CMD.<img alt="" border="0" src="http://pixel.wp.com/b.gif?host=indianexpress.com&#038;blog=53855017&#038;post=2756276&#038;subd=indianexpressonline&#038;ref=&#038;feed=1" width="1" height="1" />
]]>
</description>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img class="size-full wp-image-2756305" src="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/harbhajan-singh-m.jpg" alt="MS Dhoni-Amrapali, MS Dhoni, Amrapali, Harbhajan Singh, Anil Sharma, sports news, sports, cricket news, Cricket" /> Harbhajan Singh came in support of MS <a href="http://indianexpress.com/tag/ms-dhoni/">Dhoni</a> after the Indian skipper resigned as the ambassador of the Amrapali group. (Source: PTI) <p>The MS Dhoni-Amrapali controversy is heating up and some new facts are popping up. Harbhajan Singh came in support of MS Dhoni after the Indian skipper resigned as the ambassador of the Amrapali group. The off-spinner was seen lashing out at the group and claimed they didn&#8217;t present the Indian team with the &#8216;promised&#8217; villas after winning the ICC 2011 World Cup.</p> <p><strong><a href="http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/harbhajan-singh-lauds-ms-dhoni-for-dropping-amrapalis-brand-ambassadorship-2756097/">READ: Harbhajan Singh lauds MS Dhoni</a></strong></p> <p>Replying to Harbhajan Singh&#8217;s claims, Anil Sharma, Amrapali CMD asked Harbhajan to take his villa as it has been allotted to him.</p> <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"> <p dir="ltr" lang="en">Harbhajan&#8217;s villa is allotted. He can take it whenever he wants.I stand by my gift-Anil Sharma,Amarpali CMD <a href="http://t.co/hgUlRNjDee">pic.twitter.com/hgUlRNjDee</a></p> <p>— ANI (@ANI_news) <a href="http://twitter.com/ANI_news/status/721266096737796096">16 April 2016</a></p></blockquote><img alt="" border="0" src="http://pixel.wp.com/b.gif?host=indianexpress.com&#038;blog=53855017&#038;post=2756276&#038;subd=indianexpressonline&#038;ref=&#038;feed=1" width="1" height="1" />
]]>
</content:encoded>
<wfw:commentRss>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/harbhajan-singh-can-take-his-villa-whenever-he-wants-says-amrapali-cmd-2756276/feed/
</wfw:commentRss>
<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
<media:thumbnail url="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/harbhajan-singh-f.jpg?w=450"/>
<media:content url="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/harbhajan-singh-f.jpg?w=450" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">Mumbai Indians team's practice session</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://0.gravatar.com/avatar/3bfbb228f2cd05d4c81e005d0a694622?s=96&d=identicon&r=G" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">tanujlakhina</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="https://indianexpressonline.files.wordpress.com/2016/04/harbhajan-singh-m.jpg" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">
MS Dhoni-Amrapali, MS Dhoni, Amrapali, Harbhajan Singh, Anil Sharma, sports news, sports, cricket news, Cricket
</media:title>
</media:content>
</item>
<item>
<title>
IPL 2016: KKR beat SRH by eight wicket, Gambhir smashes unbeaten 90
</title>
<link>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/live-cricket-score-kkr-vs-srh-ipl-2016-kolkata-knight-riders-sunrisers-hyderabad-streaming-video-2756208/
</link>
<comments>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/live-cricket-score-kkr-vs-srh-ipl-2016-kolkata-knight-riders-sunrisers-hyderabad-streaming-video-2756208/#respond
</comments>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 15:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 20:50:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</dc:creator>
<category>
<![CDATA[ Cricket ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ Sports ]]>
</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
http://indianexpress.com/?post_type=article&p=2756208
</guid>
<description>
<![CDATA[
Gautam Gambhir smashes unbeaten 90 to power KKR to eight-wicket win over SRH in Hyderabad on Saturday.<img alt="" border="0" src="http://pixel.wp.com/b.gif?host=indianexpress.com&#038;blog=53855017&#038;post=2756208&#038;subd=indianexpressonline&#038;ref=&#038;feed=1" width="1" height="1" />
]]>
</description>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img class="size-full wp-image-2756626" src="http://images.indianexpress.com/2015/04/gautamgambhirl.jpg" alt="Gautam Gambhir led from the front and remained unbeaten on 90. (Source: BCCI/IPL)" /> Gautam Gambhir led from the front and remained unbeaten on 90. (Source: BCCI/IPL) <p><em><strong>Chasing
]]>
<![CDATA[
a modest total, KKR put the innings on track with a fluent 92-run stand. After Robin Uthappa&#8217;s departure, Gautam Gambhir powered the chase and remained unbeaten on 90. Earlier, Umesh Yadav rocked SRH with a fine spell, picking three wickets.</strong></em></p> <p><strong><a href="http://indian
]]>
<![CDATA[
express.com/cricket/scorecard/shkr04162016181034">Scorecard: KKR vs SRH, IPL 2016 (CLICK HERE)</a></strong></p> <p><strong>AS IT HAPPENED! </strong></p> <p>1920 hrs IST: Gautam Gambhir&#8217;s unbeaten 90 powers KKR to eight-wicket win over SRH</p> <p>1912 hrs IST: KKR need 15 off 19 for their second win of the season</p> <p>1904 hrs IST: Gambhir, meanwhile, is in a hurry. Hitting Saran to all parts of the park. Moves into the 70s</p> <p>1900 hrs IST: WICKET! Rahman cleans up Russell. KKR lose their second</p> <p>1851 hrs IST: WICKET! Reddy&#8217;s back of the hand delivery traps Uthappa in front. KKR 92/1</p> <p>1849 hrs IST: Gambhir works it away for a single and brings up his second consecutive FIFTY of the tournament</p> <p>1845 hrs IST: Gambhir is two shy of another fifty. Has been in top touch this tournament for the KKR &#8211; leading from the front</p> <p>1839 hrs IST: FOUR! Short and wide from Karn and Gambhir cuts it into the gap for another boundary</p> <p>1830 hrs IST: SRH have managed to keep it tight but have failed to taste any success in the first eight overs</p> <p>1827 hrs IST: THAT&#8217;s FIFTY for KKR in the eighth over of the innings. Both Gambhir and Uthappa looking good</p> <p>1824 hrs IST: FOUR! Short from Henriques and Gambhir puts it away in fine fashion</p> <p>1819 hrs IST: Karn Sharma to bowl his leg-spin. SRH need a wicket, even two here</p> <p>1815 hrs IST: KKR off to a brisk start in the modest chase. Both Gambhir and Uthappa rotating the strike well &#8211; doing nothing silly in the middle</p> <p>1804 hrs IST: FOUR! Uthappa hits another boundary, straight down the ground. He&#8217;s timing the ball sweetly in the middle</p> <p>1801 hrs IST: FOUR! Uthappa goes straight and hits another boundary</p> <p>1800 hrs IST: Bhuvneshwar Kumar has a nice shape going his way. SRH must have a slip in place, wickets hold key in modest defence</p> <p>1754 hrs IST: Saran, the debutant into the attack. Uthappa is off and running. Gambhir, too, is in good touch</p> <p>1750 hrs IST: KKR openers Gambhir and Uthappa are out in the middle for the modest chase</p> <p>1735 hrs IST: IPL 2016: SRH post 142/7 against KKR in Hyderabad. (Morgan 51, Ojha 37; Umesh 3/28)</p> <p>1732 hrs IST: WICKET! Sharp work in the deep and Reddy falls short of his ground. Run-out. SRH 141/7</p> <p>1727 hrs IST: Umesh has bowled well today. Mixing it up nicely in the middle and unleashing the effort ball here and then. Ends with figures of 3/28</p> <p>1726 hrs IST: WICKET! Morgan hits the Umesh delivery straight to Shakib in the deep. 128/6</p> <p>1722 hrs IST: SIX! Short, and Morgan hits it way back into the stands. Brings up his FIFTY &#8211; top knock under pressure</p> <p>1719 hrs IST: WICKET! Excellent teamwork by Chawla and Russell in the deep ends Ojha&#8217;s innings. SRH 117/5</p> <p>1715 hrs IST: SIX! Morgan goes straight, goes big. Ends a good Shakib over with a maximum. SRH 115/4 after 17 overs</p> <p>1710 hrs IST: Four to play, SRH are 105/4. Two set batsman in the middle, they should eye 150 from here now</p> <p>1709 hrs IST: SIX! Short and wide from Morkel, and Ojha gives it a whack. Brings up the 100 for SRH</p> <p>1707 hrs IST: On return, Narine goes wicketless to end with figures of 0/26</p> <p>1704 hrs IST: SIX! Narine into the attack and he concedes a maximum early in the over. First six of the match. SRH have momentum on their side now, important they make most of it</p> <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"> <p dir="ltr" lang="en">Not one over in the powerplay&#8230;not one in the death. Gambhir, quite rightly, handling Narine&#8217;s comeback carefully. <a href="http://twitter.com/hashtag/SRHvKKR?src=hash">#SRHvKKR</a> <a href="http://twitter.com/hashtag/IPL?src=hash">#IPL</a></p> <p>— Aakash Chopra (@cricketaakash) <a href="http://twitter.com/cricketaakash/status/721302578185658369">16 April 2016</a></p></blockquote> <p>1701 hrs IST: FOUR! Morgan ends the 14th with a reverse-sweep to the ropes, SRH collect 13 from the over. 86/4</p> <p>1700 hrs IST: FOUR! Chawla drifts on the leg-side first ball and Ojha just helps it on the way</p> <p>1658 hrs IST: Seven overs to play, and Gambhir introduces Chawla into the attack</p> <p>1656 hrs IST: FOUR! Action replay? This one slightly better as Morgan had more power behind this inside-out hit</p> <p>1655 hrs IST: FOUR! Morgan joins the act now, hits Narine inside-out over covers for another boundary</p> <p>1653 hrs IST: FOUR! Just the fifth boundary of SRH innings. Ojha opening the face of the bat, using the pace to help it to the ropes</p> <p>1651 hrs IST: Narine has conceded just eight off his first two overs. Has become slower through the air, but still effective</p> <p>1647 hrs IST: WICKET! Hooda hits the Russell delivery straight to Umesh Yadav in the deep. SRH lose their fourth. 50/4</p> <p>1644 hrs IST: FIFTY up for SRH in the 10th over of the innings. It&#8217;s turning out to be a good toss to lose for Gambhir. His bowlers have given him a top start</p> <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"> <p dir="ltr" lang="en">Warner &amp; Gambhir wanted to bat &amp; bowl resp. but plan not going SRH&#8217;s way after losing 4 quick wkts. Great bowling by Umesh so far. <a href="http://twitter.com/hashtag/SRHvKKR?src=hash">#SRHvKKR</a></p> <p>— Mohammad Kaif (@KaifSays) <a href="http://twitter.com/KaifSays/status/721297586791952385">16 April 2016</a></p></blockquote> <p>1637 hrs IST: Sunil Narine to bowl 9th over of the innings. He returns to scene after a long time, and a remodeled bowling action</p> <p>1630 hrs IST: WICKET! Last ball of the powerplay and Umesh traps Henriques in front to pick his second wicket. SRH struggling at 36/3 after six</p> <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"> <p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="http://twitter.com/hashtag/SRH?src=hash">#SRH</a> in DEEP trouble&#8230;don&#8217;t see them clawing back into this game from here. <a href="http://twitter.com/hashtag/SRHvKKR?src=hash">#SRHvKKR</a> <a href="http://twitter.com/hashtag/IPL?src=hash">#IPL</a></p> <p>— Aakash Chopra (@cricketaakash) <a href="http://twitter.com/cricketaakash/status/721293301228249088">16 April 2016</a></p></blockquote> <p>1627 hrs IST: FOUR! Width on offer and Henriques lashes hard at that Umesh delivery. No slip, and it races to the fence</p> <p>1622 hrs IST: Early spin! Shakib into the attack now. Pressure on SRH</p> <p>1620 hrs IST: Eoin Morgan is the new man in. SRH off to a poor start, need a steady now</p> <p>1619 hrs IST: WICKET! Clever change of pace from Umesh, and more importantly a better length, and Warner chips it to Suryakumar Yadav at covers. 23/2</p> <p>1618 hrs IST: FOUR! Short from Umesh and Warner just helps it into the gap. Third-man was up and Warner placed it to perfection</p> <p>1617 hrs IST: Moises Henriques joins Warner in the middle</p> <p>1615 hrs IST: WICKET! Morkel generates extra bounce and Dhawan could only edge it to Uthappa behind the stumps. The keeper takes a sharp catch. 18/1</p> <p>1612 hrs IST: FOUR! Dhawan eases one straight down the ground for first boundary of his innings. Was in complete control on that occasion</p> <p>1610 hrs IST: Just five coming from Yadav&#8217;s first. SRH 14/0 after first two overs</p> <p>1605 hrs IST: Umesh Yadav to bowl from the other end. Dhawan would like to get some runs under his belt today</p> <p>1602 hrs IST: Morkel creates the early chance but over-stepped. Warner survives</p> <p>1600 hrs IST: SRH openers Dhawan and Warner are out in the middle. Morne Morkel with the new ball for KKR</p> <p>1538 hrs IST: The team sheets are out, here&#8217;s a look at the two XIs</p> <p>SRH XI: D Warner, S Dhawan, M Henriques, D Hooda, AA Reddy, E Morgan, N Ojha, K Sharma, B Kumar, Mustafizur Rahman, B Sran</p> <p>KKR XI: G Gambhir, R Uthappa, M Pandey, S Al Hasan, Y Pathan, S Yadav, A Russell, P Chawla, S Narine, M Morkel, U Yadav</p> <p>1531 hrs IST: Team News! KKR make three changes, Sran to make his IPL debut for SRH</p> <p>1530 hrs IST: TOSS! SRH elect to bat first against KKR</p> <p>1525 hrs IST: Looks like a good pitch to bat on. There is some grass, so expected to hold it together. Waqar Younis feels it might get slower as the game progresses</p> <p><strong><a href="http://www.jansatta.com/news-update/live-cricket-score-kkr-vs-srh-ipl-2016/86453/">FOLLOW THE MATCH IN HINDI HERE</a></strong></p> <p><strong>The build-up</strong></p> <p><strong><a href="http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/ipl-2016-kkr-vs-srh-hope-to-get-tactics-right-2755591/">Against KKR, SRH hope to get tactics right</a></strong></p> <img class="wp-image-2756114 size-full" src="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/sunrisershyderabadl.jpg" alt="Live Cricket Score, live score cricket, cricket live score, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr srh live, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh match live score, kkr vs srh live streaming, kkr srh ipl live score, kolkata knight riders vs sunrisers hyderabad, kkr srh ipl live streaming, live streaming" /> Live Cricket Score, KKR vs SRH, IPL 2016: Sunrisers Hyderabad look to improve after a dismantling against RCB in the IPL opener. (Source: PTI) <p>Sunrisers Hyderabad (SRH), now in their fourth season, have struggled to attain the visibility that some of the more ‘glamorous’ teams have achieved. On Saturday at Uppal, they play host for the first time this year to a team, Kolkata Knight Riders, who have thrived on publicity and have two IPL crowns.</p> <p><strong><a href="http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/ipl-2016-dont-judge-us-on-basis-of-one-match-says-kkr-captain-gautam-gambhir/">Don&#8217;t judge us on one game, says Gambhir</a></strong></p> <img class="wp-image-2755425 size-full" src="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/gautam-m.jpg" alt="Live Cricket Score, live score cricket, cricket live score, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr srh live, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh match live score, kkr vs srh live streaming, kkr srh ipl live score, kolkata knight riders vs sunrisers hyderabad, kkr srh ipl live streaming, live streaming" /> Live Cricket Score, KKR vs SRH, IPL 2016: KKR pulled off a superb win against Delhi Daredevils, but lost badly to MI. (Source: PTI) <p>Kolkata Knights Riders captain Gautam Gambhir on Friday expressed confidence that his side can put up an impressive performance in their IPL match against Sunrisers Hyderabad on Saturday, notwithstanding their loss to Mumbai Indians earlier.</p> <p><strong><a href="http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/ipl-2016-we-will-put-our-best-foot-forward-against-kkr-says-tom-moody-2755435/">We will put our best foot forward, says Tom Moody</a></strong></p> <img class="wp-image-2755437 size-full" src="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/srh-m1.jpg" alt="Live Cricket Score, live score cricket, cricket live score, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr srh live, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh match live score, kkr vs srh live streaming, kkr srh ipl live score, kolkata knight riders vs sunrisers hyderabad, kkr srh ipl live streaming, live streaming" /> Live Cricket Score, KKR vs SRH, IPL 2016: The Sunrisers lost by 45 runs to RCB in Bengaluru earlier this week. (Source: PTI) <p>Seeking to shrug off the defeat in their IPL campaign opener against Royal Challengers Bangalore, Sunrisers Hyderabad would look to put their best foot forward in Saturday’s match against Kolkata Knight Riders, coach Tom Moody said on Friday.</p><img alt="" border="0" src="http://pixel.wp.com/b.gif?host=indianexpress.com&#038;blog=53855017&#038;post=2756208&#038;subd=indianexpressonline&#038;ref=&#038;feed=1" width="1" height="1" />
]]>
</content:encoded>
<wfw:commentRss>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/live-cricket-score-kkr-vs-srh-ipl-2016-kolkata-knight-riders-sunrisers-hyderabad-streaming-video-2756208/feed/
</wfw:commentRss>
<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
<media:thumbnail url="http://images.indianexpress.com/2015/04/gautamgambhirt.jpg?w=450"/>
<media:content url="http://images.indianexpress.com/2015/04/gautamgambhirt.jpg?w=450" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">GautamGambhirT</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://2.gravatar.com/avatar/efbc65766bbaaca1081ee9d0b1ac9a1c?s=96&d=identicon&r=G" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">sahilmalhotra1</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="https://indianexpressonline.files.wordpress.com/2015/04/gautamgambhirl.jpg" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">
Gautam Gambhir led from the front and remained unbeaten on 90. (Source: BCCI/IPL)
</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="https://indianexpressonline.files.wordpress.com/2016/04/sunrisershyderabadl.jpg" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">
Live Cricket Score, live score cricket, cricket live score, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr srh live, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh match live score, kkr vs srh live streaming, kkr srh ipl live score, kolkata knight riders vs sunrisers hyderabad, kkr srh ipl live streaming, live streaming
</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="https://indianexpressonline.files.wordpress.com/2016/04/gautam-m.jpg" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">
Live Cricket Score, live score cricket, cricket live score, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr srh live, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh match live score, kkr vs srh live streaming, kkr srh ipl live score, kolkata knight riders vs sunrisers hyderabad, kkr srh ipl live streaming, live streaming
</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="https://indianexpressonline.files.wordpress.com/2016/04/srh-m1.jpg" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">
Live Cricket Score, live score cricket, cricket live score, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr vs srh live, live kkr vs srh, kkr srh live, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh IPL 2016 live score, kkr vs srh match live score, kkr vs srh live streaming, kkr srh ipl live score, kolkata knight riders vs sunrisers hyderabad, kkr srh ipl live streaming, live streaming
</media:title>
</media:content>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Mitchell Starc ties the knot with girlfriend Alyssa Healy
</title>
<link>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/mitchell-starc-ties-the-knot-with-girlfriend-alyssa-healy-ipl-2016-2756151/
</link>
<comments>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/mitchell-starc-ties-the-knot-with-girlfriend-alyssa-healy-ipl-2016-2756151/#respond
</comments>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 14:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 15:00:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<dc:creator>
<![CDATA[ ]]>
</dc:creator>
<category>
<![CDATA[ Cricket ]]>
</category>
<category>
<![CDATA[ Sports ]]>
</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">
http://indianexpress.com/?post_type=article&p=2756151
</guid>
<description>
<![CDATA[
Mitchell Starc and Alyssa Healy tied knot and the auspicious occasion was attended by members of Australia's men's and women's teams. <img alt="" border="0" src="http://pixel.wp.com/b.gif?host=indianexpress.com&#038;blog=53855017&#038;post=2756151&#038;subd=indianexpressonline&#038;ref=&#038;feed=1" width="1" height="1" />
]]>
</description>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
<img class="size-full wp-image-2756210" src="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/strac-wedding-m.jpg" alt="Mitchell Starc, Alyssa Healy, Mitchell Starc weds Alyssa Healy, Alyssa Healy Mitchell Starc, Mitchell Starc wedding, sports news, sports, cricket news, Cricket" /> Mitchell Starc gets clicked on The Day with Alyssa Healy. (Source: Instagram) <p>Mitchell Starc on Friday tied knot with his girlfriend Alyssa Healy. While Starc is Australia&#8217;s premier fast bowler, Healy is a wicketkeeper for Australian women&#8217;s side.</p> <p>Starc is away from national duty after his ankle injury and his expected to make a return to the side for the West Indies tri-series. He is missing the ongoing IPL too.</p> <p>The auspicious occasion was attended by Australia&#8217;s men&#8217;s and women&#8217;s teams, including Nathan Lyon, Josh Hazlewood, Pat Cummins and Ellyse Perry.</p> ( function() { var func = function() { var iframe_form = document.getElementById('wpcom-iframe-form-4db7378213c72a6e8a388fb7b9a7be33-571985bd89035'); var iframe = document.getElementById('wpcom-iframe-4db7378213c72a6e8a388fb7b9a7be33-571985bd89035'); if ( iframe_form &amp;&amp; iframe ) { iframe_form.submit(); iframe.onload = function() { iframe.contentWindow.postMessage( { 'msg_type': 'poll_size', 'frame_id': 'wpcom-iframe-4db7378213c72a6e8a388fb7b9a7be33-571985bd89035' }, window.location.protocol + '//wpcomwidgets.com' ); } } // Autosize iframe var funcSizeResponse = function( e ) { var origin = document.createElement( 'a' ); origin.href = e.origin; // Verify message origin if ( 'wpcomwidgets.com' !== origin.host ) return; // Verify message is in a format we expect if ( 'object' !== typeof e.data || undefined === e.data.msg_type ) return; switch ( e.data.msg_type ) { case 'poll_size:response': var iframe = document.getElementById( e.data._request.frame_id ); if ( iframe &amp;&amp; '' === iframe.width ) iframe.width = '100%'; if ( iframe &amp;&amp; '' === iframe.height ) iframe.height = parseInt( e.data.height ); return; default: return; } } if ( 'function' === typeof window.addEventListener ) { window.addEventListener( 'message', funcSizeResponse, false ); } else if ( 'function' === typeof window.attachEvent ) { window.attachEvent( 'onmessage', funcSizeResponse ); } } if (document.readyState === 'complete') { func.apply(); /* compat for infinite scroll */ } else if ( document.addEventListener ) { document.addEventListener( 'DOMContentLoaded', func, false ); } else if ( document.attachEvent ) { document.attachEvent( 'onreadystatechange', func ); } } )(); <img alt="" border="0" src="http://pixel.wp.com/b.gif?host=indianexpress.com&#038;blog=53855017&#038;post=2756151&#038;subd=indianexpressonline&#038;ref=&#038;feed=1" width="1" height="1" />
]]>
</content:encoded>
<wfw:commentRss>
http://indianexpress.com/article/sports/cricket/mitchell-starc-ties-the-knot-with-girlfriend-alyssa-healy-ipl-2016-2756151/feed/
</wfw:commentRss>
<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
<media:thumbnail url="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/strac-wedding-f.jpg?w=450"/>
<media:content url="http://images.indianexpress.com/2016/04/strac-wedding-f.jpg?w=450" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">Strac-wedding F</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://0.gravatar.com/avatar/3bfbb228f2cd05d4c81e005d0a694622?s=96&d=identicon&r=G" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">tanujlakhina</media:title>
</media:content>
<media:content url="https://indianexpressonline.files.wordpress.com/2016/04/strac-wedding-m.jpg" medium="image">
<media:title type="html">
Mitchell Starc, Alyssa Healy, Mitchell Starc weds Alyssa Healy, Alyssa Healy Mitchell Starc, Mitchell Starc wedding, sports news, sports, cricket news, Cricket
</media:title>
</media:content>
</item>